</salt>

School of applied technology



Mariana Pereira

Two of my greatest strengths are my creative mind and my ability to take initiative. Having formerly worked as an architect I was able to hone in my creativity in an organized manner which I also continuously do as a full stack developer. My previous experiences have enabled me to quickly adapt and find solutions to new demands and problems.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

General

JavaScript Typescript Python

Backend

NodeJS ExpressJS REST GraphQL MongoDB/PostgreSQL

Frontend

React/Redux HTML jQuery CSS/SASS/styled-components Bootstrap

Tools and technologies

Visual Studio Code
Handlebars/Mustache
Mocha/Jest
Docker
Git/GitHub
AWS
Cloud Platforms (MongoDB Atlas,
Netlify, Heroku, Contentful)
TDD
Agile work methods
Adobe Suite
Figma

Links

<u>LinkedIn</u> <u>GitHub</u>

Languages

English - fluent
Portuguese - fluent
Spanish - Intermediate
French - Beginner
Swedish - Beginner

EDUCATION & TRAINING

Full Stack JavaScript - School of Applied Technology </salt>

Intensive three month training program for full stack web development with a focus on TDD, mob programming, Agile and applied learning.

Master in Architecture - University of Lisbon

September 2015 - December 2017

Master Degree in architecture with an emphasis in sustainability in construction and remodelations

Bachelor Degree in Architecture - University of

September 2012 - June 2015

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Architect

April 2018 - October 2020 Designed small residential renovation projects for Portuguese clients.

Math and English Tutor - Pontos nos Is

September 2017 - May 2018

Tutored children aged between 10 and 16 in both Math and English, having increased their grades greatly by the end of the year.

Summer Camp Coordinator - Acude Aventura Radical February 2015 - April 2018

During my time as a summer camp coordinator I have managed a team of 7 people and was responsible for 94 children. As well as co-coordinated and empowered a team with more than 20 people to work with 500 children on the same day.